My name is Rob and I am the ET Whisperer
and that is a clever name myself and Kalina fell into
so it was a great synchronicity
and the reason that it fits is because
throughout the last 7 years
I've contacted or channeled over
100 diffrent ET consciousnesses.
I've not done collective consciousnesses as much,
but I have tapped into some of those,
some Archangels
but for some reason
the ET thing sticks with me very well
and it fits the energy very well
so thats where I like to stay in
My connection process is a little different
than the rest of the channelers.
That seems a little odd to some people
but basically what I'm gonna do,
I'm gonna breathe for a little bit and then
I'm gonna make some very loud Oming sounds
and then I'm gonna breathe a little more,
and then Aridif will join us.
The Oming sounds are resonant tuning.
You guys can join along if you want.
You guys can breathe all you want.
That Oming gets your Chakra's vibrating,
and that's how it helps me connect to Aridif.
So enjoy yourself and remember every question you ask
that's personal in nature
is a reflection from your own consciousness.
And Aridif will look at your energy,
he'll see any energy that it connects to,
your higher self, your oversoul, Archangels, whatever.
He'll see it connecting to it and then
he will be able to reflect it back
from his perception and his connections, so
remember to have fun!
Remember to enjoy yourselves and...
I love you guys.
(Oming sounds)
Greetings to you all this is Aridif.
That is Ａ･Ｒ･Ｉ･Ｄ･Ｉ･Ｆ
and this is it spelled.
I know that many of you have queries of your own
in this evening, we will begin in one moment.
But first
we wish to discuss the co-creation of
the magnitude in which you have all placed
your own energy, that you have all
placed your own excitement and love,
time and effort into...
...making come to fruition for all others
in your experience, and outside of it, in this evening.
First of all,
when all of you understand that
many are aware of what is happening
in this moment, in this time
...but there are many who have no
concept or clue that this event
in the way it is happening, is happening
or that it is happening at all, in this evening.
But yet those who are around us are still affected
by your excitement,
by your co-creative collective consciousness.
By your own desires and excitement you build,
and this is what we have shared
from the beginning of the time
that we have come to Rob
and all of the time that we have connected to
Treb-BOR-yit-Ne
and all of humanity.
We've connected to humanity for thousands of years,
and different races of humans,
or different time periods of humans.
Different geography's than what we are now,
but we always have the capacity to teach and to share
what it is that we desire to teach and share
with all of you.
That is that you create
your own reality from thought.
You create your own reality
from your conscious mindset.
That in your co-creation with others
that you are creating not only the physical structure
around you
but all things that accompany the concepts
of exchanging energy.
Whether you are walking down the street
and seeing someone nod and wave,
that is a co-creation but it also created from yourself.
This dynamic is difficult for many humans to comprehend
"How are we able to create and co-create?"
"Is the one across from me, the one who is
being created or is co-creating with me?"
What we would say to this is, it does not matter!
What matters is your own excitement in the moment.
Your own ability to create
what you desire in each moment.
You take your energy and place it in many thought formats.
You place it in many thought forms
as you go through the day.
You think about the hardships
that you've had in your existence,
and that, because you are who you are,
and because of your history,
you should create more of that and
that is what your life is and you have settled for it.
But we understand that all of you
who are here in attendance
are starting to see greater aspects of yourself.
In each moment
you see yourself connecting
to other people who's excitement
matches. You're co-creating experiences
with entities who are not aware
of conscious mindset or what the word channeling means,
but yet you see them liven up,
you see their eyes sparkle,
you see them come to an excitement
in their own capacity to help co-create more excitement.
That is what this evening is about,
is excitement.
It is about creation, it is about co-creation.
What we have shared and what we will always share
is that we have a part in sharing our love with you.
You may do with it as you desire,
you may take the love that we send you
and use it for your own manifestations
of excitements, your own co-creations
or you may leave it at the door.
We do not mind what you do with the love we give you,
we just wish to send you this love.
And this is why we express in all time periods
that above all things that have been spoken of
in this evening by ourselves
is that you are loved is the most important point
When you say the words that you are loved,
it brings you an experience that feels different
than when someone expresses that I love you.
When I love you,
this means that two separate entities
that are segregated from one another
share love and send it to another person
who than accepts it but...
...when you are loved,
then that is all that needs to be said.
Love is around you.
If you desire it, you can accept it and
manifest with it.
Love is what creation is.
It is what all consciousness is made from.
And you as a non-physical entity
are aligned with that energy if you desire.
To realign with yourself,
all you must do is open yourself for the experience.
Now a part of that experience is understanding
things upon a deeper level.
So what we can share with you in this evening
is perhaps give you a reflection on
the questions you desire
in order to co-create a better understanding
for you to open your own energy up to the more love
around you if you desire.
And if you do not we are still here to share it.
You may begin with your queries at your leisure.
Ever wondered if their is intelligent
life elsewhere in the universe?
Well, I have, I've been wondering since I was a kid.
My name is Reuben Langdon.
And on March 29th, 2007, in the middle of the day,
I saw a number of strange objects in the sky.
Coincidentally, I was working on
the film Avatar at the time, playing an alien.
And ever since then I've been on a quest...
To find out if aliens really do exist and if so...
...are they here with us?
If beings of higher intelligence are here...
...what is their purpose?
Why don't they make themselves more known?
Why the secrecy?
I've asked these questions to many experts,
Yet, each seems to have a different theory.
So I thought to myself,
why not ask the aliens directly?
So that's what I've set out to do!
Well, sort of...
>> All right.
Well, here we are.
We're with Rob Gauthier.
And you channel a couple
of amazing beings.
More than a couple,
I should say.
How about you tell
us about yourself
and how did you get into this
whole channeling process?
>> Well, it's a bit of a story.
I always love explaining it.
But first, I was
a kid growing up
in a family that was
really Christian.
And Christianity was a big,
big part of my life as a child,
growing up into a
younger teenager.
At about 13, which is the
natural time of rebellion
for most, I kind of went
through this experience
where I separated
myself from it.
Growing up, I had
all these questions.
And every time I would ask the
preacher or a person esteemed
on the board of the
church directors,
or whoever, just someone
who is knowledgeable,
they never could really give an
answer that was complete to me.
It always seemed like
it just went back to,
because the Bible says so, or
because the church says so.
And I had a friend
who would go with me.
And we were both pretty
critical of the whole thing.
So after exploring that, I
kind of did my own thing.
I let science be
a big part of what
my reality was at that point.
In school, I did pretty
well with science.
I enjoyed it.
Earth science, especially.
And going through
that time period,
I distanced myself more
and more from the church.
After a few years,
I just quit going.
And not to my mother's
liking either.
But we just kept going through.
And after a few years of
just being off and about,
I started going through a
real, real rebellious stage.
And that was a very
disconnected time in my life.
I hung out with a
lot of people who--
they did the gang
things in the '90s.
So violence was part of that.
Drugs.
All of those things
were a big part.
I started smoking a lot of pot.
It wasn't an expansive thing.
It was fun.
So it was in my destructive--
>> It was a party thing.
>> Yes, it was.
Exactly.
>> Right.
Not Native American going
into the woods and--
>> No drumming circle.
>> No drumming circle, calling
in the Great Spirit Bear.
>> No.
But there were a lot of bears
there, just the wrong kind.
>> Right, right.
>> And it was fun.
And it was violent, destructive.
And it was a big
part of my life.
And I went that way until
right around the time
before I found out my son
was going to be on his way.
And I just kind of quit hanging
out with people a few months
before then.
Maybe it was intuition,
looking back.
>> A big responsibility coming.
>> Well, it was the first
time in my life I looked
at an aspect of something
that wasn't myself.
Everything was
centered around myself.
Even though I had
people who I loved
and were a part of my life,
up until then, it was just me.
And knowing this
responsibility--
the moment of
change really didn't
come till the day he was born.
He was born with a lot
of physical problems.
Cerebral palsy.
>> Did you know that right
away, right when he was born?
>> Not to the extent,
no.
They told us that
he had problems.
So when he came out, he did
not have any breath on his own.
They had to hook
him up to machines.
So I knew that
there was an issue.
But I didn't know the
extent of the issue.
>> I see.
>> They basically sent us home
and said, here's some medicine.
There's a possibility
he might have seizures.
We've seen some brain
waves that weren't normal.
So they sent me back.
And I took care of him.
And I didn't really
know the extent
of how bad it was
until he started
missing all the physical
marks. Like they'll say
at six months he's
supposed to lift his head,
and at three months, to do this.
And he missed all of them.
>> I see.
>> When he was
about two years old,
we took him back to the doctor.
And that's when I really knew.
And that's when the depression
in myself really started.
That's when the true
disconnection that I'd
experienced actually happened.
>> You were disconnected--
just the whole experience,
having a son in this state,
it was just hard to cope with?
>> Yeah.
It's the thought of knowing.
And when they tell me,
they don't tell me, hey,
your son has a problem.
They're like, he
has severe problems.
He'll never walk.
He'll never talk.
He'll probably be
like a vegetable.
And that's pretty much how
the doctor explained that.
>> Man.
Doctors.
>> Yeah, no bedside manner.
I know.
>> And then I guess,
they always say, well,
we're trained to tell
you the worst in case.
And that's not a good training.
>> Right.
Well, knowing what we know now
and what we thought, it's bad.
So it hit me like
a ton of bricks.
>> Sure.
Sure.
>> It was something that I
made myself try to cope with,
but I could not on my own.
>> Right.
>> I didn't have any
spiritual things in my life.
Before all I could
depend on was pot.
And that's what helped take the
edge off throughout my whole
teens and young 20's.
So from the time I found
out that my son's mother was
pregnant to the time he was
two, I had really pulled away
from my old lifestyle.
But now I immersed
back in it triplefold.
So it was more disconnection
than I ever experienced.
More-- my mind's going
crazy all the time.
No mental focus whatsoever.
So I go through that.
And it got real bad into the
depths of all sorts of things.
I even got into severe
drug use and pain--
I started with pain management
for a car crash I got into,
and it spiraled downhill
to the worst case scenario.
And after that, I spent many
years just kind of existing.
If I didn't get medicine,
I would be sick.
And my life really did
a tilt-a-whirl on me.
>> Right.
>> And that was the
worst time of my life.
And about seven
years into it, maybe
less than that, of really bad,
bad disconnection depression,
I finally started
coming out of it.
And I went through a lot
of steps to get there.
But the last step
included me actually
starting to see life again,
and starting to see--
and this is when I really
honed in on nature,
and I honed in on the animals.
Before I had pets, but
I never had an animal
that was connected to me.
I'd never seen it as an equal,
I'd seen it as property.
Those little changes
subtly creeped in.
And overnight it was just
an amazing difference
in perception, an amazing
difference in the way I felt.
And that's when my true
spiritual journey began.
That's when I really
started diving in.
One thing I always believed--
and science could not quench
my hunger for the desire
of how things started--
chemically, yes.
Engineering of the
universe, sure.
But never that god
that I knew was there.
>> Right.
>> So that was the one thing I
took into my beginning of this
spiritual journey, god.
And one thing too--
a lot of the times
during my whole life, UFOs,
ghosts, those two things
were really something
that my friend and I
had talked about all the time.
And there was never
an explanation
from the church or
science for either one.
And the afterlife
thing was always
something that amazed me.
I'd seen these
psychics on TV who
said I can talk to
spirits in the afterlife.
And I was very, very
skeptical, to say the least.
But some of the things they
would say would be profound.
And I thought, that's
a starting point.
Let's look into that.
I found a church that
integrated their desire
to look on the
other side of death,
so that they could bring
answers from the other side.
And they believe in God.
And they followed a
bit of the Bible
too, which was a comfort
zone, I guess, for me
from my childhood belief.
So I jumped in.
And when I went there,
they taught me meditation.
Right off the bat,
I got a reading
from the person, the
deacon, or the pastor,
whatever title he had,
and it was spot on.
He didn't know me.
No one from the church knew me.
No one had my social
media profile.
But yet, they told me
things about my son.
And they told me
things about relatives
that, at first, I had no clue.
But when I went to my
dad, who follows genealogy
and our family
tree. He said: Wow,
this person from six generations
ago had this and this.
So it was perfect.
>> So it matched up.
>> Synchronicity.
And it hit me so
hard that he could
have that kind of information.
That drew a level
of reality to me.
It drew some realness to it.
>> Well, just to back up.
When you said you started
noticing the animals
or I guess your perspective
on animals had changed,
was there a specific
event or something
that made that happen,
or did it just happen?
>> It was a lot
of little things.
For instance, the way my dogs
would come to me, instead
of just kind of--
they would always come
to get petted or something,
but they would come
and spend time with me.
Little things like that.
>> I see.
>> Going out in the woods.
As a younger person, I hunted.
It's Michigan culture.
>> Yeah.
>> I was raised here.
>> Right.
>> So I hunted all the time.
And the last time I went hunting
was right around that time.
I had a deer right in my sights.
I actually fell
asleep in the woods.
And I woke up, and this
deer is five foot from me.
And I had my gun,
unlocked the trigger,
put it right on the deer, and
I couldn't pull the trigger.
And after that, I never
went back out in the woods.
Those types of things.
Very hard, very big.
But a lot of little
things that led up
to it that really made me
understand what that connection
was a bit more than just
the animal-human perspective
that Christianity, and just
humans in general, believe in.
>> I see.
I remember you mentioned
before that you
had gotten involved with some
recordings from the Monroe
Institute.
>> Yes.
I would meditate all the time.
And I kept gaining
more experiences.
And I finally just kind
of pooped out on it,
and it just stopped.
After that, I started
looking online.
And that's when I found
the Monroe Institute.
I found some binaural stuff.
And then I found
Hemi-Sync, which was
the biggest and best out there.
It's what was claimed.
>> Right.
>> I started the Gateway
Experience course,
which was a six course--
six part per course, and then
six courses of meditation,
which increased my meditation
ability tremendously.
This is where all of the astral
projection states come in.
This is where all of the
out of body experiences--
it took my meditation to
such a level beyond anything
I thought was possible
at that point.
I had only used
meditation before to try
to open myself for communication
with spirits, dead humans.
That's all I cared about.
>> Oh, you did.
OK.
>> That was my intent
in my meditation.
>> When you were in church,
still with the church?
>> Yes.
>> OK.
The, the spirits was what
their church was involved with.
That was the whole focal
point of their church,
was to communicate with
people who had died to give
proof of afterlife.
>> I see.
>> And that was important to me.
And I thought that wasn't the
only intent for meditation.
>> Right.
>> My meditation came because,
like drugs helped pull me out
of pain and suffering, this new
excitement I found whenever I
would start to go down and
start to feel a little cruddy
or start getting back in
those low points again,
I would use meditation.
And it brought me to a new level
of feeling good, and excited,
and clear.
And I used it like I used to
use drugs, several times a day,
as much as I could.
The quantity, the quality
was important to me.
So I kept using
meditation as a tool
to help alleviate all
that stress and stuff.
So that coupled with
that contact of people
who had passed on.
Those were the real focus
points of my meditation.
And the Hemi-Sync took
me above and beyond that.
>> And can you describe
how it did that?
Or is that something you
have to buy the Hemi-Sync
and go through?
Is there--
>> It's a several step process.
So the teachings are
just tools to use.
And the vibration sounds,
basically, they sync up
your hemispheres of the brain.
>> OK.
Yeah, because binaural
beats and Hemi-Sync,
it's based on the same
concept of different tones
in different ears.
>> Yes.
Exactly.
And some of them,
and not Hemi-Sync.
I used other ones.
But Hemi-Sync was the one
that gave me technique.
Those teach you techniques.
>> Right.
>> They teach you
healing, out-of-body,
communication with
spirit, all of those.
And with those, I was
able to jump through.
Now, the experiences themselves
were so vast, and different
kinds of experiences.
The first day I started, there
was a vibration in my body
I never felt before.
It made my whole body [BUZZING].
And the chakras were
just high vibrational.
And those types of
experiences were
what hooked me in right away.
>> Wow.
>> I was skeptical,
to say the least.
So I started with
my first one saying,
well, we'll see what it does.
And the first one was a hit.
So I just kept going.
>> Wow.
>> The experience itself--
normally, I suggest to people,
if you do the Hemi-Sync,
go through it at your own pace.
But I would suggest no
less than six months,
no less than a year
to go through all six.
For me, I jumped through
them in four months.
>> Wow.
>> And I thought it
was way too quick.
But everything
happens for a reason.
>> Right.
>> And it worked out well.
>> So that led you into
the channeling state?
Or did you get to talk
to spirits, I should say?
>> I never got real contact with
spirits in the way I wanted to.
>> OK.
>> But my belief system then
was I should be hearing them
in my ears, like
audioclairancy or something.
And that should
be the experience.
But I had gotten
pictures or ideas.
And that really never happened
in the Gateway Experience.
There were times
where I was able--
>> Gateway is the church, or no?
>> No, Gateway
was the Hemi-Sync.
>> Oh, OK.
>> That part really never gave
me any kind of spirit contact.
Although, I do know
that I was connecting
to different energies.
Maybe not aware in the
moment, questioning that.
And that was something
the church had helped me
with before, to stop
questioning myself,
because that's a big, big part
of tapping into your intuition.
>> Right.
>> So I go through these.
And I get all sorts
of experiences,
out-of-body experiences,
not controlled.
And I still-- to this
day, I can astral project,
but I can't tell
myself where to go.
I can't say, I want
to go down the street
and hang out in the
bar in spirit form.
I can't do that.
>> Oh, I see.
But you can shoot
out of your body.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> And then it just kind of--
>> Every time I
connect in channeling,
that's what I'm doing.
>> And then you just--
it just floats around,
and you're just kind of
observing whatever appears
to you?
Or how does that--
>> Well, I've had
experiences like that.
But most of time, it's like
an experience going out
into a different
environment altogether.
I've experienced other planets.
I've experienced other parts of
reality here, different times.
But how I connected
to TReb was different.
I had not had an
out-of-body that
was severely powerful or very,
very deep in meaning to me.
And I had a real messed
up night that night.
I watched the Hubble
Deep space thing
for the first time, the 3D
one that they had on YouTube.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> And it touched my heart, but
it kind of made me feel empty,
like I can't go out there.
I can't be a part of that.
And it really kind of made
me depressed a little.
So I used a meditation.
In the Hemi-Sync, they go
through steps 1 through 21.
And I decided one night, well,
why don't I just go past 21.
And that was that
night of depression.
And that's when I met TReb.
And when I met TReb, it was--
>> Steps 1 through 21, and what
do you mean by going past 21?
Do they have actually
steps after 21?
>> No.
>> Oh.
>> They do 1 through 21.
And basically, when you're
meditating, you're counting.
It's a self-hypnosis.
That's what meditation is.
And each step that you
take, you go deeper in.
So step 1, you're starting
to feel less your body,
and then it goes on.
So I went past the 21.
And that's the maximum of
the Gateway Experience,
is the 21st--
They call it the 21 state.
>> What's at 21?
Can you reveal what's at 21?
>> Well, 21 state is
basically a full-blown conscious
integration.
You can connect with
your higher self.
You can leave your body.
At that point, you're at the
deepest level of consciousness
available.
>> And did you kind of in
your own mind then say OK,
we're going 22.
>> Yeah.
And I just-- and it
wasn't even a number.
I didn't go 22, 23.
>> Right.
>> I just went beyond.
Now, it's time to go beyond.
And I did it in the moment.
>> Through the veil.
>> Not deciding
before, in the moment,
and that's when I
connected to TReb,
right then.
>> Wow!
>> Now when I'm connecting to
TReb, this is very surreal.
It's very realistic.
It's just like me and you
sitting here talking today.
And that's the
first time I'd ever
left my body in such a fashion.
>> Wow.
>> Before when I left my body,
there would be tracers or sound
would be gone, or the images
were blurry, or vibrating.
It was always different,
but never this clear.
I was on a ship.
I know that much now, because
I've been back to those ships
before.
It was one of the Yit ships,
which is TReb's people.
And I was sitting there
in a room by myself.
And eventually, through
the door comes TReb.
And this, it scared
the shit out of me.
It was a horribly
menacing being that was--
you're looking up
to, 7 and 1/2 foot.
I'm sitting in this
chair, and I'm instantly
transported sitting in a chair.
I always joke, it's like a
futuristic space doctor waiting
room, because you're
just sitting there.
And there is a sign that
has this writing over here
to the right.
And it's not written in English.
But after looking at it
long enough, I could tell.
And it basically says something
to the effect: Just sit here,
and someone will be with
you soon, type thing.
And I laughed about that.
I still-- I don't
know if I made--
>> You interpreted it.
You interpreted it as sit here.
OK.
>> And I wait.
And this big gigantic
reptilian, blue green,
gigantic teeth, huge purple
eyes, just comes through.
>> Now, I'll jump ahead
just for a second.
When I come back, I
think I am insane.
I think something's
wrong with me.
I think the Hemi-Sync gave me
a brain aneurysm, or something,
because this is not real.
>> It's a crazy
psychedelic experience.
>> Yeah.
>> Beyond psychedelic
>> Beyond anything you
could ingest, entheogens,
any of that.
>> Oh, wow.
>> The silver suit, he even wore
a silver robe and gold boots.
And I'm thinking to
myself, if I were trying
to pull out the cheesiest
space futuristic suit,
what would it be?
And that's it.
And that's what he was wearing.
>> Wow.
>> He comes to me.
And it's this gigantic thing.
And I'm scared.
And I felt my energy
tighten up like a ball.
And it was very scary for
only a couple of seconds.
And after that, it dissipated.
I felt this huge sense of love.
I was able to relax.
It was almost like--
I'm trying to think--
OK, it was almost
like a sedative
at the doctor, that just
relaxed the body and the mind.
And then he came in.
And he said that
he was connected
to me, that me and him were
connected and supposed to meet.
He told me a lot
of things that I
think I know about reality
aren't necessarily the way,
there's a lot more to it.
He explained different
levels of consciousness.
He explained
different dimensions.
He explained--
>> All this in this one meeting?
>> In the first meeting, and
the first time I ever talked
to him.
>> Wow.
>> And he didn't go detailed.
Now, I didn't have the
terminology either.
>> Right.
>> And the way telepathy
works is that when--
they're using your words
to try to convey a message.
And you don't necessarily
get words per se.
It's just kind of
a group thought.
All of this coming
to me at once.
And it was so overwhelming
and so powerful
that it was hard to
remember a lot of the things
that we talked about the
first couple of times.
But the first time, I remember
it like it was yesterday.
It was so clear.
And he explains, it's
not what you think,
all these levels.
And he said, I'm here.
I'm here for you.
If you want to connect
to me, I'm here.
And I left.
And now, at this time, when
I started the Hemi-Sync,
I was full-blast.
I'm three times a day meditation
for an hour, an hour 25 each.
Plus using closed-eye technique,
where I'm just turning sounds
into vibrations and energy,
and understanding that.
It's kind of a self-taught
technique that I taught myself.
>> Basically, after learning
these meditations I would
utilize, I was
hooked on meditation.
And in my mind, to miss
a day of meditation
is like missing
breathing oxygen.
But after that, it was
so intense and so odd,
I skipped meditating for over
four days before I reconnected.
>> After the TReb experience.
>> Yes.
And after that point, I
was hesitant to go back.
And I questioned myself
more than I did just
about any time in my life.
Even more than the--
>> Questioning your sanity.
>> Yes, my sanity, everything.
I had talked to my ex-wife,
she was my wife then, about it.
And she said, this meditation
is doing something to you
probably.
I wouldn't worry
too much about it.
You seem lucid.
You seem OK.
So finally I...
>> And the rest of your life was
getting better at this point,
because of the meditations?
>> Oh, yes, yes.
By this time, I had already
spent several months
with the church, several months
after the church meditating.
So my life was really
getting smooth again.
>> And relationships, and
your son, and your viewpoint,
and all that was getting better?
>> Yes.
It was getting a lot
better at that point.
>> OK.
So you knew the meditations were
working, not in a negative way,
but in a positive way.
>> Sure.
Sure.
And it became so
much a part of me.
I hated to miss those four
days, but I was just so,
so questioning myself, and if
I should keep going with this.
And it was a big question
mark at that point.
But the question remained.
Can I do this again?
Can I meet this being?
Can I ask him questions?
Because I really didn't get a
lot of chance to talk and ask
questions.
It was more of him saying,
hey, this, this, and this.
>> Right.
>> Are your ears open?
Yes, they are open now.
So I go back, and I meditate.
>> You go through the 21 cycle.
>> Yes,
and I go past them.
>> Now the 22 cycles.
>> Yes.
>> So now you know how to
get there through this--
>> Easily now.
>> Through this process.
>> Yes.
And the part of me
that was hesitant
said, I'm just going to do it.
And I went past.
I reconnected to him two
or three times after that,
just basic conversations.
Who are you?
>> And it was just as
visceral as the first one?
>> Yes.
>> Each time?
>> Each one just as vividly
as the last, just as real,
just as strong.
Each time it got
a little easier.
But about the fourth
or fifth time--
>> It got easier to get there,
or just the whole experience?
>> On my own sanity, on
my questioning myself,
it got a little easier.
>> I see.
I see.
>> It wasn't so jolting.
>> Right.
OK.
>> And it was jolting the
first time, the second, third.
I go, and I--
the fourth, fifth time
I go, and I ask him,
how do I know you're real?
How do I know I'm
not going crazy?
How do I know something's
not wrong with my mind?
And he said, talk
to your friend.
And this is the same
friend who I grew up with,
the same friend, Scott,
a dear friend of mine
since we were kids.
>> Right.
>> How do I know you're real?
He said, go talk to Scott.
And when you do, don't
tell him about me,
just talk to him as your friend.
And there should be something
in there that will help you.
And I go, OK.
No later than a day, my friend
gets a hold of me, and says:
Hey, I've got this really
cool UFO documentary
I've been watching.
It's really amazing.
He sends me the link
to it, and I watch it.
And on that documentary,
they started
talking about channeling.
Now--
>> So you didn't know
about channeling.
>> Nothing about channeling.
I knew about mediumship
from the church.
>> Right.
>> That's what their
whole deal was,
but I never heard
the term channeling.
And although I had
seen it in the church--
people getting messages
directly through them--
I never knew
exactly what it was.
>> I see.
>> I just thought that was
that medium's way of bringing
in the information.
>> Sure.
>> So I watch it.
And there's-- only out of
the whole hour and a half
documentary, it's like
a five-minute clip.
And out of that, they
talk about the Law of One,
which was an ET
contact channeling
from the '80s, the "Law
of One, Ra Material."
>> OK.
>> Carla Rueckert and the crew.
And during that time,
they mentioned that.
And I'm sitting
there in excitement,
but not really
knowing anything more
about what I should
be listening for.
And right at the end of it, this
guy says: This, in my opinion,
is the greatest
channeling out there,
second only to Jane Roberts
and the "Seth Material."
One sentence.
That sentence grabbed me
more than the other five
minutes of talking.
>> Right.
>> So that's what I checked out.
And now looking
back, I know why,
because the "Ra Material"
was pretty far out there
comparatively. The "Seth
Material" was more mainstream.
It was more about
consciousness and evolution
of the soul, which was what
TReb had talked to me about.
So I locked into that.
I looked it up, got
all the audio clips,
downloaded the PDF.
All of these things online.
>> From "Seth" and "Ra,"
or just the "Seth?"
>> Just the "Seth."
The "Ra Material" was still
out of my scope, off my radar.
>> Even though you've
seen a big purple-eyed--
>> Yes.
You would think that the
rest would be OK, right?
And I never looked
at it that way.
But I always know
there was a reason.
>> OK.
>> And when I dug in, I
found out what it was.
Seth was saying the
same thing that TReb
said, just in different terms
and different terminology.
And some of these
terms were new to me.
And I had to really
kind of focus.
Some of the words, I had no
idea what they even meant,
but I would go
through, and I studied.
And what it was,
I am not a reader.
I don't read.
I listen, like audio
books are my thing.
>> Same way.
I'm the same way.
>> It's a cognitive thing.
>> I've been audio-listening
to your book.
>> Nice.
>> I have it in the PDF format,
and I have it on my iPhone.
It's a process, but
still, I can go through it
much faster by listening to it.
>> Oh, nice.
I need a program like that too.
It's helpful, to say the least.
That's how I retain
that information.
So I find this one little clip.
It's like an hour
and 50 minutes.
And it's excerpts of
"Seth Speaks, the Eternal
Validity of the Soul."
>> It's the clip on YouTube?
>> There's one on YouTube, and
there was one downloadable one
that just had the excerpts
from this guy who enjoyed that,
he read,
and it was professionally done.
And I listened to it, and it
changed my whole perspective
on a lot of stuff.
And it was so powerful
and so resonant
with what TReb had
already said to me.
And when I heard
that, it reconfirmed
that maybe I wasn't making
this stuff up in my head.
>> Right.
>> And this is something I
never have said publicly before,
but in that four-day period
where I stayed away from
the meditation and
didn't go back to TReb,
I actually went to the
emergency room and said,
I had this experience.
I might be going crazy.
>> What did they say?
>> The doctor was cool.
He's like, you're playing around
with those binaural beats.
He goes, meditation,
sometimes you
go into a lot of
subconscious places.
He said, you probably just had
some kind of weird experience.
He said, I wouldn't worry about.
>> Oh, OK.
>> Which gave me relief.
>> But you go like open the
emergency doors, and say,
I've seen a green,
seven-foot tall, blue eyes.
It's real.
Gold boots, silver robe.
>> They would have locked me up.
>> So you didn't go in
that dramatic, that big.
>> No, very lightly.
>> You just signed
the documents--
>> What are you here for?
I had an experience I
need to talk to you about.
It was very nice though.
He was cool.
>> All right.
>> If it would have been
a different doctor--
>> He didn't give you a
shot and strap you to a bed,
and hook you up to
a bunch of machines.
>> I'm sure if I
had another doctor.
>> Yeah, if you got that
wrong doctor, you probably--
>> I would have
been there, yeah.
And it's amazing to see how
the mainstream thinks about it.
>> True.
>> But I lucked out, really.
It wasn't luck, but
you know what I mean.
I get done with that.
And I have those experiences.
And from there, it
just kept going.
Now, most people who have heard
TReb or Aridif on the radio
or on YouTube, they might not
know the whole story about it.
I worked with TReb for two
years in meditative state
before I ever channeled.
I really had no
interest to channel.
At the end of the two
years, I felt like I
had learned all I could learn.
Of course, being the
human ego, I was like,
I know everything now.
>> I know the universe.
>> Yeah.
>> It's like Keanu
Reeves in the Matrix.
He's like, I know Kung Fu.
>> Yeah.
Instantly.
Yeah, that was beautiful.
>> But so after two years,
though, you're like, yeah.
>> I know what I can know.
And I wanted to find out
how to teach it to people.
>> Right.
>> I thought I was ready
to teach people, and I was.
So I knew that it was
possible to channel.
I'd seen Jane Roberts do it.
And by that point, I had
looked up Darryl Anka.
I had heard of Kryon,
even though I never
checked out a lot of
that work at that point.
And I'd seen just
a very few others.
Back when I started doing this--
>> Esther Hicks
and Abraham Hicks.
>> I'd never even heard
of her until I met Kalina.
Kalina is the one who's like,
have you ever heard of-- who?
And she's like you
really are a channeler.
Because so many
channelers are so
oblivious of other
spiritual teachers,
just because they're
in their own groove.
>> I just did another interview.
And they-- she was saying
the exact same thing.
I was like bringing
up all these names.
She was like, ah, I don't know.
The name sounds
familiar, but purposely,
I don't go and see
that stuff, because I
don't want to plagiarize
or say anything that--
I don't want anybody
to think that I'm
copying their material.
>> Well, that was a
concern of mine, too.
When I started to
jump ahead a little,
when I started channeling,
I cut myself off
from all other channel material.
I said, I want--
and this was for me,
not for anyone else--
I want to know what's coming
through is legitimate.
I had huge filter
issues in the beginning.
But to jump back,
I work with TReb.
I told him, I want to channel.
I want to share this.
But I want you to be
there for the answers,
because there's still stuff
I'm probably not sure of.
And if there is, you
need to be there.
The channeling idea was cool
to me, and we worked with it.
>> So when you said you want--
you asked him to be there, but
in essence, channeling, you're
asking him to come through.
>> Yeah.
>> OK.
You had that conversation with
him in this meditative state,
which again, I'm assuming
is still as visceral as ever.
>> Yes.
>> It's still like--
>> Never a time was dull.
>> OK.
So it all felt just like we're
having a conversation just now.
Only you're on a
ship always, or--
>> No.
We were everywhere
at that point.
The first time was a ship.
And after that, most, like
I'd say probably 75% or more
of the time, I'm with
him on his planet,
just different
parts of the planet.
But yeah, I've been
everywhere with him.
>> Well, I know I don't want
to get out of order here,
but what's his planet like?
What is that like?
>> Oh, it's beautiful.
It's gorgeous.
When you're looking
up at the sky,
it's a beautiful,
beautiful purple sky.
>> Purple sky?
>> It's hard to explain, too,
because the shade of purple it
is, there really isn't a shade
of purple I found to show
people, like this is the purple.
But they have tons
of red plants.
>> Red plants?
>> Very beautiful green water.
It's gorgeous.
>> Green water?
>> Yeah.
OK.
So we're talking.
Are all the plants red?
Do they have green plants?
>> Oh, no, no.
It's all red, just
different shades of red.
There are a couple ones
that are different,
like so different in red,
they're almost not red,
like yellows.
And a couple of them
are purple, but not--
it's like a red-purple.
It's all shaded red.
And I don't know if that
has to do with their star,
or if it has to do
with the actual plants
the way I can perceive it.
>> What about their
dirt and the ground?
What is that like?
>> I've never seen it.
It's all covered with stuff.
>> It's covered with red leaves.
>> Yeah.
Well, just like grass.
There's a different
kind of grass.
It's more fluffy.
It's like--
>> Moss?
>> Not like moss, more--
it's-- I can't think
of the plant's name.
It's stuff that people eat.
It's like a mix of kale
and a dandelion, I think.
It's hard to explain.
>> Kale and a dandelion.
>> It's fluffy, and it's leafy.
>> Not wheatgrass.
>> It might be.
I'm not versed on the--
>> On the whole
health food stuff.
>> Yes.
Not yet.
I'm working on that.
>> All right.
Interesting.
>> But it's all over the ground.
So you don't see exposed ground.
And I never went digging.
Every time I'm there--
>> Sprouts.
>> Yeah, sprouts.
That's a good one.
Yeah.
I like that.
It's kind of like that.
Yeah, but leafy,
a little leafier.
>> All right.
OK.
>> Yeah.
>> Wow.
It's fascinating,
because I've never
heard like this, like
you were in that world,
so visceral, and so real.
I didn't understand that's--
I think before we were joking
at the seminar you went fishing
with TReb.
But I'd never thought it
was actually going fishing,
like we're here at a lake.
>> Yeah.
>> It's that real
that you could go--
>> That real.
>> I wonder what kind of fish?
Did you ever see any fish?
>> No.
They do have
underwater life there.
They have big, big lizards too.
Go figure.
There are these gigantic--
I'd say probably
about six-foot long.
>> Like iguanas?
>> They're more-- they're
actually very similar,
TReb said, to their third
den-- or the second density,
their second density life,
which is, they kind of look like
Komodo dragons,
but more upright.
They're really long, really
big, very thick scaling.
They have the same color
skin as TReb's race,
different shades darker though.
More towards like a
forest green-blue,
if that makes sense.
>> And you've seen these?
>> Yeah.
I've seen those.
Those are-- the major life
on their planet are those.
>> Birds at all?
>> Yeah, they've
got flying things.
They've got little
flying things that--
they don't look
like birds, though.
They look almost like--
>> Dinosaurish?
Pterodactyls?
>> No, they're actually
very mammal-looking.
>> Oh, mammal-looking?
>> Yeah.
They're the only things on the--
>> Bats?
>> Not like a bat, either.
They have wings.
They fly, but they're real boxy.
>> Boxy.
What do you mean by boxy?
>> Squared.
They're very squared
in their features.
>> Interesting.
>> Yeah.
>> Wow.
>> It's different.
>> This is fascinating.
I feel like we don't
even need to channel.
We can just talk all
day about this world.
>> There's been some worlds
that I've seen too before.
I have talked to people,
like CGI artists, and said,
I want to describe this
to you and make it,
but it's such a process.
And nobody has an
interest in doing it,
unless there's money
involved with it.
The few people who've
done artwork for us
usually do the entities that I
channel, like TReb or Aridif.
Vashta does those, and Eduardo.
>> Do you think then
when CGI artists--
I used to run a visual
effects company,
so I know some of these
model makers come out
with these fascinating designs--
do you think they're
actually tapping
into some alternate planetary
consciousness out there
as opposed to it being
originally created,
or maybe pieces of different
planetary consciousnesses?
>> I guarantee they're
channeling 90% or more of it.
>> Oh, wow.
>> They're even-- and it's
something like it's a conundrum
where is it that
everything exists,
or is it that this
universe is so big,
that it has to exist somewhere?
Or is it just whatever
you think, you create?
It doesn't really matter,
because what they're doing
is real.
I've seen some of the
special effects stuff
that people have done in
movies or video games.
And it's like,
I've seen something
almost exactly like that,
or something very similar.
Enough where you couldn't
notice the difference to someone
who doesn't live there.
>> Right.
Wow.
>> So it's truly inspiration.
That imagination part of
us is us tapping into that.
>> Yeah.
Fascinating.
So you spend two years
going to this world,
having these conversations.
And it's your idea then
to finally talk to TReb
and say, hey, why don't we try
this whole channeling thing?
>> Yeah.
>> And what does he say?
Of course, I'm sure.
>> Yeah.
He said, yeah.
That's one of the
paths we can take.
>> Awesome.
And did he give you
tips on how to do it?
Or were you, by this time,
versed enough to say,
OK, this is what
we've got to do, TReb.
How did that work?
>> No, it's actually a
combination of the two.
And it was never me going,
hey, I think this will work.
I went out on the internet.
Obviously, the
internet was great.
There wasn't a lot
of stuff there.
So I searched out
psychic mediums.
I knew a guy who worked with
the team of the "Law of One"
material, that after the "Law
Of One" material was written,
he worked closely with
the main channeler there,
Carla Rueckert.
So I worked with him
and talked to him.
And he gave me a lot of
really great information.
I had looked up online a
couple of channeling books.
And now I realize,
probably, some
of the same people
that I'm aware of today
and just didn't know
was them back then.
>> Right.
>> And worked with TReb.
And TReb helped
me out with a lot.
And then I just kind of borrowed
a little from everything
until it was perfect.
And then I found my own mix.
It was a garden variety of
a little bit of everything.
>> What got you through?
What was the catalyst
to bring TReb through?
What was your first channeling
experience, I guess?
>> Well, my first channeling
experience, I set up a camera.
My then wife was there to
kind of monitor me and make
sure nothing went too crazy.
That was a concern of mine.
I got this entity
coming in my body.
I don't want to
lose control or--
you know, the Christian
part of my mind...
>> Hulk out!
You have this big green
alien coming through you,
you might. Did that
ever go through you mind?
>> A little bit of that.
>> OK.
>> At that point,
I trusted TReb.
I'd come to love him
like a dear friend.
But there's still the unknown.
Why would this entity come and
choose me out of everybody?
Why?
My Christian beliefs tapped
on my shoulder a few times.
So I wanted to be careful.
I wanted to be good.
I recorded myself, and it
was amazingly horrible.
>> Amazingly horrible.
>> Yes.
>> OK.
Can you describe
amazingly horrible?
>> Yes.
The voice that
people hear TReb now,
even if they go back four
years, it's not the same.
It's a little different.
And the accent's the same, the
type of talking that he uses.
But the inflections
are different.
And the yeses are
much more vibrant.
And like when he says,
yes-- that "ye-e-e-s",
really excited-- that
wasn't there then.
It was very flat and monotone,
and kind of filtery too.
There was just--
I could tell all of
TReb wasn't getting in.
So I practiced a few more times.
But when you get to know
me, you know about me,
I don't wait for anything.
I don't wait till
everything's perfect.
I just jump headfirst, fly
by the seat of my pants.
So I immediately went
to the YouTube waves.
I want to share this.
And my first channeling
was actually a lot better.
In the couple of times I
had tried between then,
I probably only did
maybe 6 to 10 channelings
between the first one and
the one I put on YouTube.
>> And when you describe
6 to 10 channelings,
or six channelings
or so before you--
and you're recording yourself,
are you asking questions?
Is it just you in the room?
I mean, how do you--
is there somebody else?
Well, you said your wife-- is
she there to help facilitate?
>> Yes.
At that point, the
first couple ones
was just letting TReb talk.
I told him, you
just come through
and say what you want to say.
I'll share something.
If it's usable, we
can put it on YouTube.
So address people.
And that's the first
couple of times.
And then after that, my then
wife would ask a few questions.
I let one of my friends try.
So it was basically trial
and error, just playing
around the first time.
>> So I guess the
information was still good.
It was just-- you say
when it was horrible,
it wasn't the
information was horrible.
>> Right.
>> OK.
>> And some of the information
came through a little odd,
just the verbiage
on it was weird.
You could tell it
was like having
someone who first learned how to
speak English be able to talk.
>> Right.
OK.
Well, that's what
I was wondering.
And maybe this is a
question for TReb later.
Does he have to learn English?
Or is it all translated by you
via vibrational translations,
vibrational frequencies?
>> My best understanding
is that, basically--
like when I go to channel,
I'm using the same techniques
in a quicker way
than I used to when
I would leave my physical body.
So I'm leaving, and
part of TReb comes in.
So when he's in, he's
mixing his energy with mine.
So it's running through
my chakra systems,
but also accessing
the brain part.
And in that brain part is
the whole English language,
my experiences, all
of my personality.
So he has the opportunity
to access that.
So English, it wasn't
that the English was bad,
because he knew English
by knowing my mind.
It was the way of
trying to express it.
Like Aridif and TReb,
still to this day,
sometimes they might get hung
up on a word, so they'll stop.
>> Right.
>> And they'll search
for the word or find one
that's as compatible
as they can.
So sometimes when-- like the one
that's most known, Aridif, when
he says, you must do
this, he's not saying,
you have to do this.
He's saying, if you want
what you're desiring,
this is the best way.
>> Right
>> So little things like that.
But then it was much more
disproportional than it is now.
>> I see.
So it was more of a
translation glitch--
>> Right.
>> Than an actual understanding
of the language or knowing
the language.
It's not necessarily
what's happening.
It's not like he went and had
to take a course in English 101.
>> That would be rough.
Yeah.
But yeah, absolutely.
It's a translational
vibrational thing.
My vibration at the time,
it wasn't what it is now.
I was learning all
this cool stuff,
but I hadn't applied
very much of it.
What I did learn
and applied helped.
And it was really six months--
>> In some way, you're
translating too.
You have to raise your level.
He has to bring his level down.
So there has to
be this kind of--
and then there's a growth,
I'm assuming, since then.
Like you said,
it's gotten better.
So you're able to meet
each other's frequencies.
You're going up there,
him coming down here.
So that's evolved
over the years.
>> Yes, absolutely.
That's the perfect way,
too, to explain that.
It's something where
it's amalgamation
of two consciousnesses.
And it's a concerted
effort on both
of our parts to co-create that.
And I couldn't get up to him.
He could always come
down to me, but I just
couldn't get up to him.
And the more I channeled,
the more I felt his energy.
And the more I felt
his energy, the easier
it was for me to integrate
certain parts of the teachings.
And in the teachings, a lot of
the stuff about self-creation,
relaxing, the way
to perceive reality
started clicking easier.
So after the first six
months of channeling,
I was 10 times better
than the first one.
And in the first
year of channeling,
I was 10 times better than that.
And it kept going.
And it's like any
job that any person
does with their motor skills.
Muscle memory comes into play.
Well, this is energetic
muscle memory.
And that's how it's applied.
It's the more you do and repeat,
the better you are at it.
And that's why even to this
day, I get better at channeling.
>> I see.
>> This time last year,
channeling was great.
It was smooth.
People resonated with it, but
now it's a whole new level.
And this is why you
see the veterans
out there who've channeled
their entire life;
Darryl Anka, and
Nora, and Wendy.
All those great
channelers, they've
been doing that forever.
It's their connection.
TReb and Aridif actually
have a term for it.
It's called building a bridge.
And each time you
channel, you're
putting a new peg in, or a new
screw, or a new plate of metal.
And the bigger the
piece comes, it's
the bigger realizations
you have in yourself.
I had points in my channeling
where I didn't learn anything.
Whenever I'd listen back
to a session, I was like,
I already knew that.
But when I started
really learning things
about my own life
on my own terms,
then it would shine
through on the channeling.
And then it would open
up more synchronicities.
And it wasn't that the
information wasn't new.
It's just the way I
perceived it was old.
So when I changed my
perceptions and my energy grew,
that allowed that energy
to come in a lot better
with understandings
and synchronicities
to apply itself.
>> So would that make the
channeling then better, better,
more defined, or in a better--
more terminology?
Or because you were able to
have that perspective on it,
did you think that
helped the channeling?
>> Absolutely.
And that was another thing.
My English skills have zero.
When I went through
school, I sucked at it.
I could speak English.
>> Just like me.
>> Yeah.
And it's not something
that I was great at.
>> Right.
>> But the more I cared
about how I talked,
because I realized--
and Kalina has been my
number one helper in that.
Every time I throw a
word that doesn't exist
or one that's mispronounced,
she helps me with that,
because she knows, they need
that too to reflect back on.
>> I see.
>> But the more
energy I opened up,
the more clarity came with
it, the easier it was for them
to find the translation, not
only of energy, but words.
>> Interesting.
So TReb started coming in,
and you're checking in.
Are you still going and doing
your meditations with him
at the same time
during this process?
Or is the process of
channeling, is it the same
as going into the meditations?
Are you trance channeling,
I guess,
in a sense where --
are you conscious
of what's happening
during the channel?
>> Now, it depends.
There are three types of
channel states that I do.
All of them are
trance channeling.
The first and most
common occurrence
is just like when
I visited TReb.
I'm going to visit him.
I'm there with him astrally.
I perceive him in real-time,
just as real as we are.
And that happens the most.
And while I'm
channeling down here,
not conscious of anything
that's being said,
I'm hanging out with him.
Going fishing with TReb.
>> Right.
Right.
>> And the second level
is the same thing.
I'm out of my body.
I'm experiencing something.
But usually, it's something
that needs to be seen by me.
And this can be a lot
of different things.
TReb showed me time periods.
He showed me different
planets, different animals,
different vegetation,
just all sorts of stuff
that at a later time comes in
for referencing that I need.
So that happens very seldomly.
>> When you say, come in for
reference, in what sense?
Like the conversation
we're having here,
and you can
reference that stuff?
>> Yeah.
Like sometimes,
people are like, yeah,
I met this reptilian
being that was so and so.
And so I was like, oh,
that's the same one
that TReb showed me.
Or I wonder what happened
in this timeline.
It gives me a better
understanding.
And I don't understand
what it is in the moment,
but in reflecting later, I
always get what's going on.
>> I see.
>> So that's the second
most common occurrence.
And then the last one is where
I'm like in a deep meditative
state, where everything's
just kind of blacked out,
sometimes colors,
sometimes things like that.
And I'm able to hear what's
going on in the session.
Now, if I channel 100 times,
probably 85 to 90 of them
are me and TReb hanging out.
All of them, but one of them
would be the deep meditation
where I'm hearing the session.
And this only
occurs when there is
something I really need to hear
in that moment in the session.
So it very rarely occurs.
>> Do you ever go in and out,
like you're hanging out with
him, and all of a sudden you
get sucked back into the room?
>> No, never.
It's always with
TReb all the time,
or he's showing me
something, or then.
And the second most common
one where he's showing me
something, it's not with him.
It's me separately by
myself seeing these things.
So that rarely ever occurs.
Out of 100 times, maybe 14
times I'll be doing that.
So it's not very-- and it's
probably less than that,
but I'm trying to give a scale
for people to understand that.
>> Now, do you--
since starting the
channeling, since having
these conversations with
TReb, the meditations,
have you become more--
instead of just applying
these things to your life,
have you noticed your
own intuitiveness
or psychic abilities, or
anything else happening
in these past few years?
>> Absolutely.
The integration process.
And this is something
that's fairly new to me.
I've been doing channeling in
the sense of public channeling
since about 2010, late 2010.
And in that time,
I was always aware
that TReb's energy
was around me,
but it never went past that.
My life, my intuition
was good, but it
was no better than where I was
when I first started meditating
and learning to receive.
In the last year, year
and a half-- well,
it's probably closer
to two years now--
I've actually been more
conscious of TReb and Aridif
as they come through.
I can hear TReb give me messages
while I'm in the wakened state.
I feel more of
his consciousness.
My personality even is more
the style of TReb, where--
like TReb, he loves everything.
He wants to
experience everything.
And I find more of
that energy in me.
And there's always been
a part of that for me.
I've always enjoyed
enjoying things,
but to a different extent.
I could feel that combining
with TReb's energy.
So it's like an amalgamation.
And this goes with
psychic ability.
It goes with everything.
There's times where I grab
something and walk it over
to Kalina.
And she's like, I was just
going to ask you for that.
Or things simple like
that, like picking
a movie that she
had wanted to watch,
or a song that she
was dying to hear.
So those things.
And that shows a great deal
about both of our connection
too as well.
But meeting Kalina was probably
one of the energetic shifting
points on a lot of things.
When I met Kalina, it's just
the energy shifted so much.
I finally found a partner
who was on the same journey
that I was.
The same excitements.
She met me through
the work I was doing.
She was helping me
edit videos and stuff
as we developed a friendship
for a couple of years.
And then as my divorce
happened with my ex-wife, then
me and her got together.
And we started a relationship.
And her excitements
and my excitements,
because they're on the same
level, we reflect that.
So our psychic ability helps.
The efforts of the
work has helped.
I was just-- when I
first started channeling,
I was doing it for fun.
I was doing it for the benefit
of other people, which I still
am.
But I had a daytime job.
I worked that job
10 hours a day.
>> I was going to say, how in
the world could you meditate
for as long as you did
for the first two years,
and still maintain a
job, and have a son?
And that's crazy.
Did you sleep?
>> Well, the first hour and 25
minutes, that was pretty easy.
The first one in the
morning before all the kids.
Because I used to
babysit, so I was at home.
>> Oh, wow.
>> I could work from home.
And when these four to
six kids would come over,
I would be able to meditate
before they got there, and then
once at lunch time when
I put them all for a nap,
and once after Jeremy.
He would get home from school
after the kids would leave.
And then I would be able to
put him to bed, and then do it.
>> So you figured
it out somehow.
>> I did.
>> You managed to
get those several--
two to four hours a day?
>> Well, three of the
meditations were an hour
to an hour and 25.
My closed-eye technique didn't
require me to be anywhere.
I could still be
present with you.
Like right now, I'm
closing my eyes.
I can hear you.
I can hear Kalina, so I'm OK.
And if I didn't need my
eyes, I could literally up
to six to eight hours a day
do the closed-eye technique.
Whenever I didn't need my eyes,
they were shut all the time.
I was dedicated.
I was like--
>> Wow.
That's awesome.
>> Yeah.
I was like--
>> I'm taking notes.
>> An addict for meditation.
>> Yeah.
>> It was.
I was addicted to it.
>> Do you still meditate then?
>> The only meditation I need
now is when I connect to TReb.
I do it so frequently, that
that is my meditation now.
>> I was going to say--
because it sounds
like a meditation.
You're going to this deep--
you're going to another planet.
Jeez.
That's awesome.
>> Well, in all honesty, though,
it's something that I found
about people in their
spiritual journey.
And something that just
recently was brought up
in a conversation.
When you reach a certain
point of integrating
with these beings or integrating
with your higher self, whatever
it is, when you feel
good about your life
when you're living
that vibration,
there's not always as
much need for meditation.
So when I meditate and connect
my TReb, I'm integrating.
But during the day now,
I'm integrating, too,
because I used that meditation
to pull myself out of suffering
and pain to start with.
And then I used it
to hone my skills.
My skills are here.
They're strong.
I don't have very much
suffering anymore.
I'm still human, so a
little bit here and there.
So now there's not
as much a need.
And the time I spend with TReb,
I'm doing this now as a living.
So when I'm doing it once,
twice, three times a day,
that's my meditation.
It works.
>> Awesome, awesome, awesome.
Well, in addition to
TReb, you channel Aridif.
>> Yes.
>> And recently
I heard Metatron.
Who else do you channel?
And then maybe we can
get into a little bit
of what led up to bringing
in these other entities.
>> Sure.
>> Let's start with Aridif
before we get into anybody
else.
>> OK.
>> Because he's the
other most known.
It's almost like--
lately, have you
been channeling
Aridif more than TReb?
>> Much more.
Much more than TReb
even at this point.
There is a high
resonance for him.
One of my friends
who makes videos,
he knows that I'm kind of a
modest person in a lot of ways.
And he puts up this
thing, "Greatest Channeler
In The World on YouTube."
And I said, dude, well,
you didn't even tell me.
You would have asked
me to take it down.
I said, no, I wouldn't have.
But still.
He said something that
really clicked with me.
He said the wisdom
and essence of Bashar,
because a lot of
people know Bashar
as a very wise high energy
being, and the heart
center of TReb, which
TReb's a huge love bucket.
Everybody loves that.
And he said, that's
what Aridif encompasses.
And that's why Aridif is his
favorite channeled being.
So people are dying
for Aridif right now.
They want to have time with him.
They want to hear
what he has to say.
Brilliant, brilliant being.
He is to TReb what
TReb is to me.
>> Oh.
>> So like when you look at
me, TReb is like maybe a future
version of myself.
And it could be looked at
in a lot of different ways.
But he's like a guide to me.
He's a higher density,
higher knowledge
being that I pull from.
>> TReb is to you.
>> Yes.
TReb, for my
information and energy.
And TReb does that with Aridif.
TReb's a fifth density being.
And Aridif's a
sixth density being.
So energetically,
it's a higher energy.
>> And do TReb and Aridif--
I assume, they do communicate?
They know each other?
>> They know each other well.
I had heard stories about
Aridif before I ever
connected with him.
Back when I heard it--
because most of these entities
don't have names of their
own, they just have energy.
>> Right.
>> And they give us names,
because we're humans,
and we need names to identify.
So TReb would talk about a
being called Deneb Cygnus.
And that's the Deneb,
like the star Deneb,
and Cygnus, the
constellation of the Swan.
And he said, this entity
named Deneb Cygnus,
and then he would tell
a story about him,
or tell a story about
information that Deneb Cygnus
had shared with him.
Well, eventually, I found
out through the book
that I did about TReb and his
people, that that was Aridif.
And Aridif gives us that name.
Aridif used that name with
humans a long time ago.
Let me-- yeah, and I'm
jumping ahead of myself.
So let me give a little
introduction to Aridif.
Aridif is an Ancient
Pleiadian entity,
but he lives in the
star called Deneb.
His race moved out
of the Pleiades star
system, which tens of
thousands of races live there.
They pulled their race out,
because energetically, they
needed a different--
he explained it
as, we needed room to grow.
But what I think is the
collective consciousness
of a race is very
similar to a star.
And in fact, that's why they
incorporate so much energy.
If it's a smaller
collective, it only
needs a little space to grow.
But when you have these
huge consciousnesses
and you have a lot of them,
they need energetic space.
And that is shown by the
star that they travel around.
And Deneb is this gigantic,
huge, supermassive,
like 150 times the
size of our sun.
And that's where his
race needed to go,
because they grew into that.
They sprung into a huge--
and when you listen
to Aridif, you
can tell more than just
his sentient energy, more
than his wisdom, he's
just huge expanded.
They're at the level
right before you
leave physical
reality altogether
and join the
oversoul energy back
in the planetary collective.
So I mean he's this huge being.
And now they inhabit this star.
And a lot of people ask about--
they don't know
what he looks like.
And there's some art out there
of him, and it's beautiful.
Kalina did art too.
She's been able to see
him too in her mind's eye.
Never TReb, but Aridif.
They had a past life where
she had met Aridif when
he physically came to Earth.
>> When he was Deneb.
>> Back in ancient Egypt.
>> When he was known as Deneb?
>> Well, no.
The Aridif name was one
that was known to Earth,
but TReb never gave me
that identity until later.
So he was still known as Aridif
when I first heard of him,
but TReb, for whatever reason,
gave me the Deneb Cygnus name.
>> So back in the Egyptian days,
he was known as Aridif as well?
>> Well, he said the name came
from the era and how they knew
him.
So maybe they knew
what star he came from,
and back then they might
have called it Aridif.
>> Oh, I see.
>> I still don't
know the specifics,
but I think that's what it is.
>> So maybe in Egyptian times,
that's what they called them.
>> Right.
>> OK.
>> And he hung out
with Egyptians.
He just recently
alluded to the fact
that he had hung out with
South African tribes,
that he hung out with
Egyptians, that he hung out
with Indians, and some
Southern American tribes.
So he has been on the Earth
manifested as a physical being
in order to co-create
with Earth before,
kind of like an energetic
quarantine, where
it was kind of interference.
And that's a difficult,
long subject to get into.
But he has co-created
with humans.
And I think that him
understanding humanity
before he came here, even though
it was a much older version,
gave him a great opportunity
when he teaches to have
it really resonate with people.
Plus the amount of wisdom that
comes out of him is ungodly.
It's just beautiful.
>> So Aridif used to interact
with the human race back
in the day; South Africans,
Egyptians, probably more.
But has it been a while then?
Is this like his--
he took a break,
and now he's back.
And humanity is like, oh,
wow, look at humanity.
Or has he been
constantly monitoring?
And do other people
channel Aridif?
>> From what I know,
no one else has.
Some people said that
his energy is familiar.
So I don't know.
But I do know that
he's been interacting
with humans for a long time.
It's been thousands of years, he
said, before he's reconnected.
And even now he's not
physically connecting.
>> Right.
>> Right now, it's an important
growth time for humans.
And a lot of the
hands-on interactions
are not appreciated
by some of the ETs.
For instance, type
1 and type 2, this
is the definition Aridif
and TReb have given.
Type 1, they'll do it in the
way that TReb and Aridif are.
>> Type 1 civilization
or type 1 ET?
>> Type 1 extraterrestrial
kind, energetic kind.
>> And what is--
>> A type 1 defined is an entity
who respects the free will
of all things,
will not interfere.
>> OK.
>> And looks above and below
them, energetically speaking.
They look above them
for inspiration, wisdom,
to incorporate.
And then below them to
redistribute that information.
They see themselves
as a part of one.
>> I see.
>> A type 2 sees division.
A type 2 being only
looks below them
for what they can
overpower or oversee.
They never look above them.
They look equal or below to
them, energetically speaking.
They also are not afraid
to interject themselves
on the behalf of
themselves or others.
For instance, a lot of
these channeled entities
that have come out
are talking about,
we are going to help you.
We're going to do this for you.
We're going to do that for you.
They're doing that, because--
some of them with great intent.
They are like, we love you.
You're messing up.
We want to help you.
But in their mind, they
know better than we do.
And Aridif and TReb
come from a place
that you guys manifest what
you want as a collective,
because that is what you want.
And we will respect
your journey.
Even if you nuke yourself to
oblivion, we will respect it.
And we will never
step in the way.
Because they know
it's a soul's journey.
The other entities look at it
as a physical thing, or even
a soul level, just at
a different interval.
So these are the
fundamental differences.
And back when Aridif did
interact with humans,
he did it from his
incarnation now,
but he also has done it
from previous incarnations
of his Denebian race.
So in that way--
>> Denebian race.
>> Yeah.
And Ancient Pleiadians
is what we call it,
because that's how he
introduced themselves.
But Denebian, that's
another term for their race.
They're from the star Deneb.
So Denebians are
another term for them.
But they have interacted
from previous incarnations.
So he dealt with humans
not just in this life,
but his past lives too.
>> Interesting.
OK.
And the overall message--
so they're obviously type 1 ETs.
And their overall message,
if you could sum it up
>> If I could sum it
up in one sentence,
it's you create everything.
And If I could sum it
up in a small paragraph,
we create that physical
reality around us,
and every aspect of it.
And when we do, we
bring the reflections
of what's inside of ourselves
to be outside of ourselves
and to co-create.
So a lot of people look at it.
Well, how is Reuben
a projection of Rob?
Well, it has to be.
There's you there,
and there's me there.
But I'm bringing you into
my reality for a reason,
as you are me.
We're co-creating a reflection.
And literally, you're
a version that I
projected into my universe.
But it's very literal
in those terms.
And people don't look
at it in that way.
They're like,
figuratively, you create.
No, literally.
And figuratively.
>> Right.
>> That's the message.
And they explore
all parts of it.
They give answers for
extraterrestrial things.
What's going on in our galaxy?
I've always termed it universal,
or galactic knowledge,
universal knowledge,
what's going on out there.
And that's an important part.
The other entities, too,
that I've channeled,
Nihal, Metatron.
Metatron would say that
the universal and galactic
knowledge is not so important.
What's important is you
growing into who you are.
So sometimes he talks about
humans distract themselves
with what's going on out there
when they can't figure out
what's going on down here.
>> Sure.
>> A different point of
view, and I respect that.
And I understand.
But TReb and Aridif bring us a
perspective that's universal.
And it gives us our
opportunity to say
how humans fit in this universal
complex, which is something
that a lot of
people have strived
to know their whole lives.
And it's very easy to see the
human race as a part of it,
but not how each individual
is a part of first the Earth
collective, then
the universalness.
It's amazing.
It's something that
Aridif sums up very well.
>> And just you
mentioned the Nihal.
>> Yes.
>> Is that a collective
consciousness?
>> Yes.
That is a collective
consciousness.
Now, the Nihal, a very
interesting story.
I'll give you a bit about them.
The Nihal are future humans.
They exist as one of our
timelines in the future.
So it's a probable reality
where we leave Earth.
Well, not all of us,
but a chunk of us
leave Earth and
become the Nihal.
And we evolve into very
short beings, about--
I can't remember-- three to
four foot, somewhere in there.
Orange-ish skin, highly psychic.
And we evolve into that.
Now, the fun part, the
part where it ties back in,
the Nihal are the race
who seeded TReb's race.
So TReb's race was a
byproduct, or a direct product,
of engineering DNA
from a human being DNA
and from a second density lizard
being who lived in, I believe,
the Capellan region, which
is where TReb comes from.
>> Human or Nihal DNA,
but Nihal being human.
>> Right.
Nihal.
But it is different
than human DNA.
And that's a good
point you bring up.
also occurs when one race
leaves their home planet
and goes to another.
The planet itself is a being.
It's a seventh density
collective being.
>> Right.
>> And then this race that
comes is also a collective
of the seventh density with
all the oversouls at the lower
seventh density.
And then they meet.
They co-create a
brand new energy.
So both collectives merge
into one, and the DNA changes.
And that's why when the human
race leaves the other planets,
they change their physical
appearance, because their DNA
changes.
Their physical body
adapts to the new merging
of the collective
planet consciousness
and their race's consciousness.
So that's a part of it too.
Now, when we're
getting into the Nihal,
the reason for doing TReb's
race, a lot of people
are like, well, if we're
evolved, why would we
be messing with DNA?
We've had that done to us.
It's not very nice.
There's such a stigma around
negative reptilian energy.
And it was hinted, not
ever directly said,
yes, this is the 100% reason.
But TReb, Aridif, but more so
than that, another entity who
I channeled in the book about
TReb's race, one of their--
I think it was the
military, ex-military.
>> The woman?
>> Yes, the woman.
She said that the reason
that they did that
was so that they could show
the entire galaxy that not
all reptilians are bad.
The stigma of Earth,
especially Earth,
was that reptilians
are negative.
They will eat your children.
They'll drug you.
They'll throw you in a cave,
and put you in their pie.
>> What is it the--
David Icke, the queen, and all
of our government officials
evolved.
Evil reptilians taking
over the planet.
>> And I get it.
>> That could--
that's probably true.
>> But not every
reptilian has that.
>> Yeah, exactly.
>> And TReb-- this is
something I commend TReb for.
He is one of the very few
channels who have come out
and said, listen, the
evil reptilians are there.
This is what
they've done to you.
This is how they're still
doing things to you.
But you're focusing on it, and
it's going to keep going on.
When you pull your focus from it
and start focusing on the power
you have, then it doesn't-- then
even if they're standing next
to you slapping people with
whips, they can't touch you.
>> Just like Jesus
and the cross.
It was much-- the
story's go as much
they were whipping
him and torturing him,
he didn't feel a thing.
>> Yeah.
And that's the
beauty part of it.
That's something that
TReb brings to us.
And the Nihal wanted
to show us that.
They wanted to show us--
I think it was targeted for
humans, but around the galaxy,
there's still a stigma
that most reptilians
are neg-- even if
they've interacted
with a good reptilian.
Humanoids, I think, because
of the damage they've
had through slavery, the
Anunnaki was half-reptilian,
the ancient reptilians,
the Earth reptilians.
Those are all bad
stories for humans.
And that's kind of built
in our DNA to fear them.
And people, like David Icke,
who've research just that part
of it and shared it, it
scares the crap out of people.
>> It continues
to feed into that.
Well, over the next
couple of days,
let's get into some channeling.
And I'd love to talk to TReb and
Aridif and explore their world
some more.
Thanks for sharing
your adventures.
>> You're absolutely welcome.
>> And we'll see
some more of you.
>> All right.
>> Thanks, Rob.